Sh-shut up! This is my first time fighting a monster.
How can you be so stupid?
Don't call me stupid!
You've never fought a monster, but you wander into a forest? That's just plain stupid! What were you thinking?
What? Now you're crying?
Geez!
What?
If you're afraid of getting hurt, then there's no way you'll get stronger! No pain, no gain, right?
You want me to teach you? Who's your opponent? I'll train you so you can beat him in less than a month!
I've been waiting.
For me? Really?
Yeah, that move you taught me was amazing! You should have seen the look on Hugo's face!
It's scary how much you've improved!
Then tell me your name!
Okay. If you can beat me.
What happened?
I know I can win now, but where did she go?